# Tony Nguyen

Tony Nguyen ↓
hello@tonynguyen.app 
818-448-1214 
www.tonynguyen.app 
www.github.com/tonynguyen98 
www.linkedin.com/in/tony-n-286465169/ in

## **▲ PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am a student pursuing a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science. I have an excellent reputation for resolving problems, adapting to changing environments, and driving overall operational improvements. I am an experienced team player with over 3 years of experience working with a team.

## PROJECTS

Software Engineer | Front-End Lead 06/2020 - present

OFF-TOP

https://github.com/Off-Top-App

- Developed various functions for the crossplatform mobile application, using Flutter. Some functions include configuring audio recording, Google Firebase authentication, and UI color themes.
- Created a back-end microservice with Spring-Boot Kotlin that utilizes Kafka Streams to stream and process aggregated objects into to a readable user report.
- Created Dockerfile images for microservices and containerized them using Docker-Compose.
- Developed a component for the web app that enforces Google Firebase authentication for user login with Angular.
- As the Front-end Lead: reviewed and approved pull requests, mentored team members, and worked with the Scrum Master to create new front-end tasks.
- Created documentation with the goal to help new members onboard with ease.

Front-End Engineer | Project 02/2020 - 05/2020 Manager

Got Gainz https://github.com/got-gainz

- Created onboarding functions to allow users to input and store their personal information.
- Created a service to persist data throughout the Flutter app.
- Assisted in the development of the UI and UX for the app.
- Created workout tracking and accompanying functions to update workout routines as users' progress their goals.
- As the Project Manager: assigned tasks, maintained the general scope of the project, and mentored developers with their tasks.

## **SKILLS**

#### **Programming Languages**

Dart, Java, Kotlin, C, TypeScript, JavaScript, PHP, HTML, CSS, SQL, Python

#### Frameworks and Libraries

Flutter, Spring-Boot, Angular, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB

#### **Platforms**

Docker, Kubernetes, Apache Kafka, Firebase

## **EDUCATION**

Computer Science 08/2016 – present California State University, Northridge, Northridge, CA

- Specialization: Software development and app development.
- GPA: 3.32
- Dean's List 2016

## **■ WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Student Assistant** 12/2019 – 05/2020 California State University, Northridge, Northridge, CA

 Performed a variety of office tasks such as Excel, file management, and phone calls.

## Intel Computer Sales 11/2019 - 03/2020 Consultant

ActionLink LLC, Porter Ranch, CA

 Partnered with Best Buy retail team members to promote Intel products, increase sales, and awareness.

**Electronics Team Member** 07/2017 – 07/2019 Target Corporation, Northridge, CA

 Offered each customer top-notch, personal service, and polite support to boost sales and customer satisfaction.